Guide to the Barbaralee Diamonstein-Spielvogel Audiovisual Materials, 1956-2018 RL.10006_AV RL.10006_AV
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Interviews, 1974-2017; 347 items
  - Audio interviews, 1974-2001; 189 items
    - Louis Dell'Olio, Donna Karan, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:53:27 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0156_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615918)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:32:21 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0310_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615965)
    - Barbaralee Diamonstein, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:12:54 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0310_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615967)
    - David Dinkins, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:18 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0043_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616197)
    - David Dinkins, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:17 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0043_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616194)
    - Arthur Drexler, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:16:12 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0091_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615890)
    - Arthur Drexler, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:16:13 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0091_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615889)
    - Arthur Drexler, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:10 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0093_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615984)
    - Arthur Drexler, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:10 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0093_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615982)
    - Arthur Drexler, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:45:17 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0094_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616042)
    - Arthur Drexler, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:31:21 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0092_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615909)
    - Alfred Eisenstaedt, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:09:30 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0165_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616060)
    - Alfred Eisenstaedt, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:03:12 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0165_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616062)
    - Alfred Eisenstaedt, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:47:32 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0299_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615976)
    - Alfred Eisenstaedt, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:47:32 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0299_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615979)
    - Ellsworth Kelly, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:18 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0056_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616148)
    - Ellsworth Kelly, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:18:41 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0056_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616150)
    - Ertegun, Rayner, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 01:03:04 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0186_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615875)
    - Ertegun, Rayner, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:13 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0186_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615873)
    - Ella Fitzgerald, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:36:40 (Box AV-061, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0294_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615991)
    - Larry Gagosian, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:28:28 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0011_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616151)
    - Larry Gagosian, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:35 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0011_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616153)
    - Henry Louis Gates, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:16 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0016_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615926)
    - Henry Louis Gates, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:08:36 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0016_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615924)
    - Henry Louis Gates, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:13:10 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0041_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616059)
    - Henry Louis Gates, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:08 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0042_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616053)
    - Henry Louis Gates, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:08:34 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0042_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616052)
    - Arnold Glimcher, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:04:16 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0016_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616205)
    - Arnold Glimcher, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:36 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0017_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616159)
    - Arnold Glimcher, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:37 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0017_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616161)
    - Barbara Gonzalez, Interview at San Ildefonso Pueblo, NM, 1981; 00:39:14 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0108_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615930)
    - Barbara Gonzalez, Interview at San Ildefonso Pueblo, NM, 1981; 00:05:29 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0108_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615931)
    - Barbara Gonzalez, Interview at San Ildefonso Pueblo, NM, 1981; 00:31:00 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0109_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616049)
    - Barbara Gonzalez, Interview at San Ildefonso Pueblo, NM, 1981; 00:31:00 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0109_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616047)
    - Agnes Gund, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:17:04 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0007_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616186)
    - Agnes Gund, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 01:02:57 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0007_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616188)
    - Kathy Halbreich, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:09:13 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0001_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616238)
    - Kathy Halbreich, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 01:03:09 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0008_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616236)
    - Ann Hamilton, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:14 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0054_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616212)
    - Ann Hamilton, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:19 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0054_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616211)
    - Ann Hamilton, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:16:28 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0055_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616241)
    - Mark Hampton, Interior Design: The New Freedom, undated; 00:31:23 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0160_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615952)
    - Mark Hampton, Interior Design: The New Freedom, undated; 00:10:13 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0160_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615954)
    - Nancy Hanks, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:45:46 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0278_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616045)
    - Alana Heiss, Richard Nonas, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1978; 00:47:03 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0269_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615879)
    - Alana Heiss, Richard Nonas, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1978; 00:33:09 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0269_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615878)
    - Alana Heiss, Richard Nonas, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1978; 00:47:08 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0270_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615945)
    - Alana Heiss, Richard Nonas, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1978; 00:33:11 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0270_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615947)
    - Carolina Herrera, Paul Smith, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:25 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0110_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615989)
    - Carolina Herrera, Paul Smith, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:22:35 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0110_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615988)
    - Sheila Hicks, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:30:10 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0147_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615961)
    - Sheila Hicks, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:26:36 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0147_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615963)
    - Sheila Hicks, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1981; 00:14:48 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0148_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616030)
    - Sheila Hicks, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:30:24 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0080_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615962)
    - Sheila Hicks, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:21:36 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0080_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615960)
    - Jenny Holzer, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:21:10 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0036_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616172)
    - Jenny Holzer, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:21 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0037_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616201)
    - Jenny Holzer, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:19 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0037_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616203)
    - Penelope Hunter-Steibel, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:29:48 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0189_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615905)
    - Hugh Jacobsen, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1977; 00:31:47 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0162_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615892)
    - Hugh Jacobsen, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1977; 00:31:48 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0162_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615894)
    - Helmut Jahn, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:31 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0200_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615882)
    - Helmut Jahn, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1983; 00:31:31 (Box AV-051, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0200_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615883)
    - Jasper Johns, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:37 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0010_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616149)
    - Jasper Johns, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:33 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0010_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616147)
    - Jasper Johns, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:31 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0053_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616200)
    - Jasper Johns, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:03:53 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0053_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616198)
    - Philip Johnson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 01:01:04 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0128_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615998)
    - Philip Johnson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:17:51 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0128_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616000)
    - Norma Kamali, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:25 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0133_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615871)
    - Norma Kamali, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:26 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0133_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615870)
    - Norma Kamali, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:31:32 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0134_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616027)
    - Norma Kamali, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:08:34 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0134_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616029)
    - Ellsworth Kelly, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 01:02:38 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0052_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616196)
    - Ellsworth Kelly, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:20 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0052_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616195)
    - Andre Kertesz, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, undated; 00:47:35 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0074_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615958)
    - Andre Kertesz, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, undated; 00:10:03 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0074_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615957)
    - Andre Kertesz, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, undated; 00:47:21 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0075_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615969)
    - Andre Kertesz, Visions and Images: American Photographers on Photography, undated; 00:47:24 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0075_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615966)
    - Robert Klein, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1987; 00:47:26 (Box AV-072, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0329_1, Digital-materials pid duke:627748)
    - Robert Klein, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1987; 00:36:35 (Box AV-072, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0329_2, Digital-materials pid duke:627746)
    - Jeff Koons, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:29 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0042_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616202)
    - Jeff Koons, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:22 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0042_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616204)
    - Richard Koshalek, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:39 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0012_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616174)
    - Richard Koshalek, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:26 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0012_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616176)
    - Larry Kramer, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:08 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0011_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616038)
    - Larry Kramer, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:26 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0011_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616039)
    - Larry Kramer, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:46:52 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0012_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616035)
    - Larry Kramer, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:15 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0053_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616021)
    - Larry Kramer, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:16 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0053_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616023)
    - Larry Kramer, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1995; 00:47:18 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0054_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615898)
    - Larry Krame, William Styron, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1997; 00:47:35 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0006_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615929)
    - Larry Krame, William Styron, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1997; 00:41:08 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0006_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615928)
    - Larry Krame, William Styron, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1997; 00:47:17 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0037_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616064)
    - Larry Krame, William Styron, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1997; 00:40:42 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0037_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616061)
    - Thomas Krens, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:23 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0030_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616213)
    - Thomas Krens, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:26 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0030_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616215)
    - Thomas Krens, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:21 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0031_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616199)
    - Barbara Kruger, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:13:19 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0003_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616220)
    - Stanley Kunitz, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1979; 00:47:13 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0255_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616068)
    - Stanley Kunitz, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1979; 00:47:15 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0255_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616070)
    - Stanley Kunitz, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1979; 00:47:25 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0256_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616073)
    - Yo-Yo Ma, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:47:03 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0327_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615943)
    - Yo-Yo Ma, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, circa 1995; 00:24:54 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0327_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615941)
    - Brice Marden, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:20 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0044_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616230)
    - Brice Marden, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:23 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0044_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616228)
    - Brice Marden, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:29 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0045_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616162)
    - Brice Marden, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:13:59 (Box AV-63, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0045_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616160)
    - Robert Mayer, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:47:11 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0277_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615959)
    - Robert Mayer, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:47:11 (Box AV-060, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0277_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615956)
    - Mary McFadden, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:46:01 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0107_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616041)
    - Mary McFadden, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:27:43 (Box AV-048, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0107_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616043)
    - Richard Meier, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:45:36 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0083_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615936)
    - Richard Meier, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:46:09 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0083_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615938)
    - Richard Meier, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1984; 00:43:01 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0084_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616081)
    - Ron Nagle, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:27:57 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0076_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616010)
    - Ron Nagle, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:31:32 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0077_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616031)
    - Ron Nagle, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1982; 00:31:33 (Box AV-046, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0077_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616033)
    - Louise Nevelson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1980; 00:46:49 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0178_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615994)
    - Louise Nevelson, Miscellaneous Interviews, 1980; 00:42:40 (Box AV-049, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0178_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615996)
    - Louise Nevelson, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:47:08 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0244_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615937)
    - Louise Nevelson, Public Policy and the Arts, undated; 00:16:04 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0244_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615939)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:21 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0020_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615913)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:14 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0020_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615911)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:07 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0021_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615995)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:19:12 (Box AV-044, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0021_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615993)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:01 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0047_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615948)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:19:07 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0047_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615951)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:36 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0048_1, Digital-materials pid duke:615876)
    - Sherwin Nuland, Singular Voices: Conversations with Americans Who Make a Difference, 1996; 00:47:40 (Box AV-045, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0048_2, Digital-materials pid duke:615874)
    - Patrick O'Higgins, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:30:59 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0239_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616003)
    - Patrick O'Higgins, Miscellaneous Interviews, undated; 00:07:38 (Box AV-054, Audio-cassette RL10006-CS-0239_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616002)
    - Nam June Paik, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:28 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0032_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616158)
    - Nam June Paik, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:25 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0032_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616155)
    - Nam June Paik, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 01:02:24 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0033_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616229)
    - Nam June Paik, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, undated; 00:31:06 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0033_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616231)
    - Earl A. Powell, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1993; 00:05:57 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0025_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616157)
    - Earl A. Powell, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1993; 00:48:30 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0025_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616156)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:30 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0022_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616221)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:31:14 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0022_2, Digital-materials pid duke:616224)
    - Robert Rauschenberg, Inside the Art World: Conversations with Barbaralee Diamonstein, 1992; 00:08:04 (Box AV-664, Audio-cassette RL10006-MCS-0023_1, Digital-materials pid duke:616216)